rtbhouse.net 2019-01-18

# Privacy Policy - RTB House | High Tech Retargeter That Makes Digital Advertising Campaigns Perform Better

We provide retargeting advertisement services to our clients. To perform these services we process certain information related to your online activity in order to serve you personalised ads which match your current interests. We collect this information by using cookies set on your browser while you visit our clients websites or other tracking technologies available on your device. Our goal is to gain enough insight from browser data to deliver personalized ads that have a high potential to be interesting for you.

## **Data Collection & Processing**

We use our tracking technologies in order to collect certain information on your activity while on our client’s website (e.g. the products displayed on the website, added to the shopping cart and/or purchased) as well as your interactions with our clients’ advertisements on other websites (e.g. how many times each advertisement was displayed, if any advertisements were clicked and if those clicks resulted in a purchase).

As this information is tied to a **unique online ID** assigned to your browser, which allows us to single you out from other users (without directly identifying you) we treat the collected data as personal data, as required by the General Data Protection Regulation ( **“GDPR”** ).

Please note that while providing our services we DO NOT collect personally identifiable information (PII) such as names, e-mail addresses, postal addresses or telephone numbers. Also, we DO NOT receive any additional data from our clients, which, along with data collected by our technology, would enable us to directly identify you.

Please note that all information related to our data processing activity, as required by the GDPR, can be accessed at: <https://www.rtbhouse.com/gdpr/>

## **The Choice is Yours**

If, after getting acquainted with the extent of data collected about your online activity, you have any concerns about the protection of your privacy you can always change the settings of your browser to disable cookies and prevent gathering any data about you through this technology. Please note that due to the common use of cookies, turning them off may prevent you from using a variety of websites. Refer to your browser’s documentation to learn how to turn off tracking mechanisms like cookies.

You can also opt out specifically from RTB House tracking technology and consequently – from processing of certain categories of your personal data mentioned above. This will prevent us from collecting any information from your browser and will result in deletion of all data previously collected.

Click the button below to Opt Out / Opt In from RTB House cookies:

Please bear in mind that if you use several browsers or different computers, you must opt out of for each browser and computer.

## **  
Data Subject Access Requests**

Under the GDPR, you are able to exercise various rights related to your personal data such as right to request access to their data or to request that the data be corrected or deleted.  
If you would like to exercise any of your data subject rights under the GDPR please contact our Data Protection Officer at: dpo@rtbhouse.com who will provide you with detailed information on specific procedure related to this issue.

## **Privacy Changes**

Please be aware that RTB House may deem it fit or necessary to update this Privacy Policy at any time. We reserve the right to make changes at any time. You will be notified of any significant changes to our Privacy Policy with a notice placed on our website.

## **Privacy Contact**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding RTB House’s Privacy Policy, write to our Data Protection Officer at: dpo@rtbhouse.com
